The Pearl Comb is a horror film directed by Ali Cook.
A doctor, hell-bent on proving a woman’s place is in the home and not practising medicine, is sent to
investigate her miraculous claim - only to discover the source of her unearthly power...
Gregory Lutey, played by Ali Cook.
Betty Lutey, played by Beatie Edney.
Lutey, played by Simon Armstrong.
The Mermaid, played by Clara Paget.
Edith, played by Roxanne Cook.
Arthur, played by Thomas Stocker.
Heather McComb (born March 2, 1977) is an American actress.
She is best known for her roles as Maggie on Party of Five
(1998–1999) and Frances Malone in Profiler (1997–1998).
The film explores themes of village, medicine, small village, 1800s, powers.
The tone is dark.